Privacy Page

Privacy Policy

Effective May 31, 2020

Thank you for visiting New Club Penguin ( “NewCP”, “us”, “we”, “ours”, “our”, or “newcp.net”). In this Privacy Policy, we cover the various data and privacy information embedded into our website and applications. In addition to outlining the types of data we collect, this Privacy Policy cites how you can delete, manage, or export your data from NewCP. We understand the big responsibility that ensues when you provide crucial data and are committed to ensuring its protection. Please review the policies herein this document before using any NewCP websites or applications.

To explain things as clearly as possible, we’ve included explanatory terms and examples. If you have any questions about the NewCP Privacy Policy, contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://newcp.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Information you provide to us

NewCP collects information about you mainly via publicly accessible sources.

1. “Cookies”, which are a small piece of information from your web browser

1. This information is intended to record browsing activity. NewCP uses it derive insights about which sections of our website are used the most, measure the performance of advertisements, and ensure application functionality especially pertaining to our moderation tools in Internet Protocol Addresses (“IP Address”).

3. Digitally transmitted requests or inquiries you submit to us via forms on the website, including the sign in and registration pages hosted on our applications.

1. We preserve records of correspondence to better serve your interests. To the furthest extent possible, NewCP tries to pseudonymize or anonymize data it collects from you while receiving submission of an inquiry via forms on the website. Preventative measures against spam may capture your IP address, especially on third-party forms or services. In the case you are submitting information to a third party beyond our servers, NewCP will provide reasonable notice.
    
2. When you utilize the features of our sign in and registration pages, we actively collect information requested from you, mainly: (i. a valid email address, (ii. penguin username and password. Both features we collect from these pages are used to sustain the user account.

Information collected from third parties

We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, as well as from other third parties. Examples of the information we receive from other sources include: social media profile information; marketing leads and search results and links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links) from our advertisement partners on certain pages unrelated to our Application. We will inform you about the source of information and the type of information we have collected about you within a reasonable period after obtaining the personal data, but at the latest within one month via email: [\[email protected\]](https://newcp.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, then these countries may not have data protection or other laws as comprehensive as those in your country, and NewCP may not be obligated to disclose certain information. We will however take all necessary measures to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable law.

Your Security Rights

Under these policies, NewCP materially provides opportunities for members to revise account information or terminate their relationship with the website. Moreover, in some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability.

In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please send a written notice to [\[email protected\]](https://newcp.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal.

Your California Privacy Rights

This conditional clause of the NewCP Privacy Policy only applies to California residents.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us via email at [\[email protected\]](https://newcp.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with NewCP, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Application or Website. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the [\[email protected\]](https://newcp.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) email, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on our website, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.

Revisions

NewCP reserves the right to create revisions to this privacy policy. These conditional policies will be revised in accordance with abuse or security concerns, regulatory or legal reasons, or to reflect changes in our policies. If a term is invalid or unenforceable, that issue is not a conditional change for any other terms outlined in this privacy policy.

_Updated May 7th, 2023_

Change Password

Resend Activation

New Club Penguin is a recreation and/or fan-made game and is in no way affiliated to Disney's Club Penguin, The Walt Disney Company and/or Disney Games.
